https://petitjeanmeats.com/customer-support/page/47/privacy-policy

OUR PRODUCT OPTIONS HAVE CHANGED: Due to production issues associated with the COVID-19 pandemic, we will be limiting our holiday mail order selections for 2020. We are sorry for the inconvenience. Thank you for letting us be a part of your holiday tradition.
HOME
RECIPES
SHOP
ABOUT
Company History
Privacy Policy
News
Fundraising
SIGN UP
Welcome, GuestShop Home | My Account | View Cart (0) | Login Privacy Policy
Customer Support
PRIVACY POLICY
This is the web site of Petit Jean Meats.51 Blue Diamond DriveMorrilton, AR 72110We can be reached via e-mail at contact@petitjeanmeats.comor you can reach us by telephone at 800-264-2475For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible).We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).The information we collect is shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site .If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.From time to time, we make our customer e-mail list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.You may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizationsPersons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by , sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizationsWith respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them .Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address, write to us at the above address.Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server that has an SSL certificate using at least 128-bit encryption. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
CUSTOMER SUPPORT
RETURNS/REFUNDS/CANCELLATION POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
SHIPPING QUESTIONS
DONATION REQUESTS
SHOP
CONTACT US
SMOKED HAM
